[funky hip-hop beat layers in]
Tired of searching for subtitles?
Ray generates them instantly: getray.app
[older Kanan] Previously
on Raising Kanan...
[Breeze] You salty
'cause your son
still makin' money without you.
I don't like nobody
makin' money without me.
That's how this shit work. son.
-[tires screeching]
-[Kanan] Raq hit our shit.
I'ma hit hers.
You wanna hit back. you gonna
have to get somethin' for it.
I'm not a dummy. Kanan.
I know you into some shit.
and I knew it
right when I met you.
This shit ain't for everybody.
Flossie here think
you cut out for this work.
but if you not. that's okay too.
Pull yourself together. Jarita.
I'ma be clear with you. Ishaq.
I'm not lookin' to be supplied.
I'm lookin' to be the supply.
You assured me that your demand
would meet my supply.
And it will.
I just gotta get
my ducks in a row.
What do you know about
Raquel Thomas?
[dramatic music playing]
I know everybody always
talkin' 'bout her.
Seem like she always
up in the mix somehow.
That's because
she's a fuckin' plague.
I need you to disrupt
her operation.
The same thing will happen
to you someday.
And I'm gonna deserve it.
Just like you.
-[silenced gunshot]
-[squelching]
[bullets ricocheting]
[laughing]
I'm Captain Baptiste.
and this is Agent Preston Tanner
from the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
So they bring in the fed
to scare me
so I can cop to some shit
I ain't do.
You do this job long enough.
you gonna make
a hell of a lot more enemies
than friends.
Just 'cause they got me ridin'
into the fuckin' sunset
doesn't mean that your work
is done. Garcia.
Where's the rest
of my fuckin' money?
You gotta give me a minute.
I don't gotta give you shit.
[Juke] You got
all your money now.
Tell me what you know
about Famous.
One of my CIs is saying
maybe cops were involved.
Truth is. no one was even
really paying attention
before the fuckin' feds tried
to connect Figueroa to Howard.
Lou gone. Ma gone.
Pops been gone.
All that's left is you and me.
I wasn't there for Lou.
But I'm here for you.
[gunshots]
Yo! What the fuck?!
Kanan killed Lou.
What-what the fuck you just say?
He put down our brother.
[Juke] Stop! No. no. no. no!
Dad. stop!
What the fuck are you doin'?
[Pastor Evans]
No matter who you are
or what you've done.
God forgives everybody.
[Juke] No. no. no. no.
[Marvin] I ain't everybody.
pastor.
[music fades]
♪ I'm a hustla. baby ♪
-♪ I'm a hustla. baby ♪
-♪ Yeah ♪
♪ I know heartbreaks Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through
The ups and downs ♪
♪ You know I get around ♪
♪ So to me. it's all a part
Of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke man
Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure. man
I gotta take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turn homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Make money
Make-make-make money ♪
♪ When shit hit the fan
We'll take money. Southside ♪
♪ Beef with the best of 'em
Done shot at the rest of 'em ♪
♪ Checks. I'm collectin' 'em
Check. boy. I'm finessin' 'em ♪
♪ Big bags of bread ♪
♪ Boy. you fuck around
Put a big bag on your head ♪
♪ 'Fore the weather break
You're dead ♪
♪ Let's get to it ♪
♪ They don't do it
Like we do it ♪
♪ Cop it. whip it
Bag it. flip it ♪
♪ Re-up. we up
G'd up. what up? ♪
♪ Runnin' 'round this bitch
Still not givin' a fuck ♪
♪ When it come to that paper
There'll be no complications ♪
♪ Ha-ha. that's right ♪
♪ Put a hole in a nigga
Right in front of you ♪
♪ Your heartbeat pacin' ♪
♪ And it's alright ♪
♪ That's how we do it
On this side ♪
♪ Niggas get to it
♪ I know heartbreaks Setbacks ♪
♪ Bitch. if I crap out
I'm sure I'ma get back ♪
♪ I been through
The ups and downs ♪
♪ You know I get around ♪
♪ So to me. it's all a part
Of the game ♪
♪ If I ain't the coke man
Or the dope man ♪
♪ I'm almost for sure. man
I gotta take it ♪
♪ No need to say shit
I'm gon' take it ♪
♪ Robberies turn homicide
It's nothin' to play with ♪
♪ Ayy. ayy ♪
[Rileyy vocalization]
[grim. ominous music playing]
[older Kanan] Losin' someone
close fuck wit' your head.
Not just 'cause they gone.
But 'cause you keep askin'
yourself why you still here.
So you try to find somethin'
in that loss.
Try to understand
what you got left to do here
when your peoples gone.
But that's just tryin'
to make sense of somethin'
that don't make no sense at all.
Some niggas die.
Some niggas live.
Ain't nothin' deeper than that.
So was the shit an accident...
or not?
[Raq] He had a gun on me.
And then Lou busted in and Kanan
turned the shit on him.
Is that a accident?
[somber music playing]
[sighs]
Shit. I don't know.
[Marvin]
Weren't for Juke steppin' in.
I woulda killed that boy
back at his crib.
[inhales deeply]
Maybe I should have.
If you're askin' me
whether he deserved
to die behind that shit.
you know I'ma say no.
He's my son.
Why you lie about him?
I don't even know.
You know. I wish I could tell
you I had a fuckin' plan.
or a vision.
or some shit like that.
I just reacted.
And I been reactin' ever since.
But I just couldn't keep it
to myself no more.
I needed you to know
what happened.
For you and for me.
[inhales]
[inhales sharply]
I told Lou-Lou I loved him
before he passed.
Held his hand.
♪♪
He wasn't alone.
[scoffs]
That night...
we was drivin' him up
to that detox...
he thought we was
gon' put him down.
He begged us not to leave him
out there alone.
Not to drop his body out...
in the fuckin' forest.
And then you just dump him
in some empty lot
with the fuckin' trash.
I panicked. Marvin.
-I didn't know what to do.
-Nah. you ain't panic.
Your head was clear as hell.
Because you did
like you always do.
You protected Kanan.
[dramatic beat]
[music fades]
[Jarita]
Okay. I'm gonna try to be as
gentle as I can.
This may sting.
-[groans]
-Sorry.
It's nothin'.
I know you got secrets. Kanan.
We all do.
But you need to at least give me
an idea of what happened here.
It don't matter. Jarita.
I wanna know that I'm safe
when I'm wit' you.
and if you got people
knockin' you around like this...
You safe.
It's about me.
I'm out here hustlin'.
just like everybody else
from around the way.
But the way I do it.
I'm just an investor.
I don't get near the work.
Somebody got near you.
[ominous music playing]
I'm not judging you. Kanan.
I just don't want anything
to happen to you.
I had a issue
wit' your employer.
-I have no idea what that means.
-Your new boss.
The lady at the club
in the Village
you been talkin' 'bout. Raq.
-Me and her competitors.
-Hold up.
You knew Raq from before we met?
What the fuck?
So you just been usin' me
this whole time to get to her.
-It's not like that.
-It's exactly like that.
I didn't know I was gonna start
havin' feelings about you.
That first time
we was together. I...
figured I'd just get
some information out you
about how shit work over there.
But then I liked you.
And we started kickin' it.
and this shit changed for me.
You been lyin' to me
all along. Kanan.
About some shit.
Not everything.
Remember that day on the street
when I told you
that this shit wasn't real?
I was right.
This shit isn't real.
You not real.
Way I feel about you's real.
Jarita.
Way I wanna take care of you
is real.
My heart's real.
♪♪
[music fades]
Got word
just before you got here
that Joaquin been put down.
Without him.
we ain't got no yayo.
We're gonna need to find
another connect.
[grim. foreboding music playing]
I know your mind
all over right now.
I get it.
But we still got a business
to run.
Fuck the business.
You fuck the business.
you fuck yourself. Marvin.
[music fades]
[loud dance music
plays from inside building]
[indistinct crowd chatter]
♪♪
Here you go.
[tense music playing]
[music fades]
I need to understand
what the fuck
is going on here.
Kanan. 'cause...
it feels like you been usin' me.
pimpin' me.
and last thing I need in my life
is another pimp.
It's like I said...
shit started for me one way...
but it's endin' up different.
I got feelings for you. Jarita.
That's the truth.
But I also got a business
that's bumping up against
the work you doin'.
So that's also true.
-You sellin' drugs.
-Like I said.
I'm more the money guy.
But me and Raq got history
that make her a problem.
What kind of history?
She's my mother.
Oh. fuck.
This shit sound like more
than it is. Jarita.
Shit ain't even about her
bein' my mother.
We was workin' together.
Shit got twisted.
Now we on other sides.
Ain't nothin' more than that.
I got a family of my own. Kanan.
and a fucked up mother too.
I know how it works.
So if you know how it work.
then you know
why I didn't tell you this shit
up front.
I'm not like Raq.
Or Flossie.
Or none of them.
I'm like you.
Just tryin' to look out
for myself
and the people
that look out for me.
You one of those people.
[somber music playing]
So you lookin' out for me?
I am.
I'm lookin' out for you too.
But don't ever lie to me again.
[music fades]
I can't say much to you. detective.
Your whole precinct
is under federal investigation.
It's-it's a fucking
hornets' nest over there.
I'm only interested
in a specific case.
Shawn Figueroa.
I just wanna know
if you uncovered
anything related to that murder.
I know you sat in on
some of those interrogations.
Only because it seemed like
the Figueroa kid
might know something
that was relevant to the work
the task force
was doing at the time.
But that case should be
the least of your concerns
right now.
It's personal for me.
Agent Tanner.
I'm tight with the kid's mother.
And I owe her
some sort of closure.
even if it isn't a conviction.
You worked closely
with Malcolm Howard.
"Closely" is a stretch.
We were on some cases together.
But if you're saying
you think I'm dirty...
We know you're clean.
Detective Garcia.
That's not what I'm saying.
I'm just telling you
that I wouldn't even trust
the fucking clocks at the 117th.
I'm trying to give a mother
who lost her son peace of mind.
That's all.
Baptiste was involved
in the Figueroa case.
[dramatic music playing]
He-he might have been part
of some questioning.
but definitely not involved
in the day-to-day.
[Tanner]
Anything Baptiste touched
is potentially tainted. detective.
Put it this way:
He didn't walk out the door
of his own volition.
I am telling you far. far more
than I should.
[music intensifies]
-[music turns ominous]
-[indistinct chatter]
[indistinct chatter]
[tapping on window]
You can't park here. Move.
My bad.
[engine starts. revs]
[Kanan] Shit was a mistake.
A fucked up accident.
I didn't even know
what I did at first.
You shot Uncle Lou. Kanan.
You killed him.
And then you lied about it
to everyone.
That was her.
Raq covered the shit up.
I woulda told y'all.
but she took control of it
and fucked it all up
just like she do.
If it wasn't for her bullshit.
I wouldn't have even been
over there like that
in the first place.
-She the one...
-Nah. nigga.
You walkin' around
like you all grown.
but meanwhile. you still blamin'
your moms for your shit.
You can't have it
both ways. Kanan.
You can't say you a man.
and then act like a bitch.
I kept my dad from beatin' you
to fuckin' death
because I thought...
I thought maybe there was
more to this.
I couldn't believe
you just did that shit.
But you did.
That was you. All you.
But you tryin' to make it
her fault.
Just like you always do.
[Juke scoffs]
[somber. dramatic music playing]
You ain't about shit. Kanan.
And...
I'm thinkin'...
maybe you never were.
[music intensifies]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[music fades]
These are Kanan's things.
Please give them to Raquel.
Olga.
Thought that was you.
Uh. just dropping off
some of Kanan's stuff
I found when
I was cleaning out the house.
You wanna come in?
I'm goin' to the airport soon.
But I-I guess I have
a few minutes.
[tense music playing]
♪♪
Hi. Come on in.
Fuck this.
[music fades]
I can't believe Kanan
even has clothes left to wear.
I found so many of them
at my house. [laughs]
I find Famous' stuff
every time I do laundry.
I was so sorry
to hear about Lou.
Must be horrible for Kanan.
So much loss
for someone so young.
My son's been through it.
[Olga] I'm also sorry for you.
Losing your brother
is heartbreaking.
Thank you.
Jessica meant a lot to Lou.
He meant a lot to her too.
Our families will always
be connected.
We have to protect the ones
we have left.
We do.
Shawn would want Kanan
to live a long and happy life.
He'd want that
for your whole family.
I want that for you.
And I want the same
for you and yours.
[Olga] I've spent so much time
asking myself if I was
a bad mother to Shawn.
If what happened to him
was my fault.
Shawn stayed with you
while we were in the shelter.
He must have said some things
about me to you.
Things that weren't so kind.
[cries]
[whimpers. cries]
This is exactly why
I didn't want to come in.
I knew I'd start crying.
[cries. sighs]
Thank you.
All Famous ever said to me
is that he loved you.
[sniffles]
Thank you.
That's nice to hear.
Even if it isn't true.
it's nice to hear.
-[sighs]
-It's true.
[solemn music playing]
Jessica told me that. uh.
Lou idolized you.
Said you were
who he wanted to be
and you were
the strongest person he knew.
That don't sound like shit
my brother'd say.
If there's one thing
losing Shawn has taught me.
it's that no one is ever
who we think they are.
Even people we love the most.
[sniffles]
[music fades]
Colombian was easy.
Nigga was damn near
naked out there.
But this other guy. Habib...
his protection on lock.
I just feel like we need
to step the fuck off.
Leave well enough alone
and shit.
We already cut Raq off
at the knees.
I want her cut off
at the fuckin' neck.
Sometimes the smartest shit
you can do is nothing.
Is that the smartest shit
we can do. Breeze?
I mean. 'cause it means
a lot to me.
comin' from a smart guy
like you.
I ain't tryin' to tell you
how to live your life
or nothin' like that.
I'm just givin' you my opinion.
Eh...
You know what? Forgive my tone.
I appreciate your opinion
and I. uh...
And even more than that.
I-I respect your...
your caution.
And you're right. by the way.
Maybe there is a...
another way to skin
the proverbial cat here. huh?
My prior partners.
your predecessors.
they coulda used some
of your restraint and care.
The guy's a diplomat. right?
[chuckles]
So... let's be diplomatic.
[both laugh]
["The Essence" playing
over speakers]
Been servin' up
so many niggas... [laughs]
My arms is tired. Like...
Shit. My dick about to be tired
from all these bitches out here
I'ma smash 'cause...
-[explosive shot]
-["Bacdafucup" by Onyx playing]
♪ The Onyx is here Bacdafucup ♪
-No.
-♪ You better bacdafucup ♪
♪ Move back. motherfuckers ♪
-Please. Please. man.
-No.
♪ Bacdafucup. bacdafucup ♪
-♪ Bacdafucup. bacdafucup... ♪
-Fuck!
Fuck am I even doing?
♪ The Onyx is here ♪
♪ Bacdafucup. bacdafucup ♪
♪ Move back. motherfuckers
The Onyx is here ♪
[mellow jazz music playing]
[indistinct crowd chatter]
[laughs]
[chatter continues]
[Baptiste] Donaldson got
so drunk on a Friday night.
that he forgot he put the perp
in his trunk
'til he rolled outta bed
Monday morning.
[laughter]
[laughter continues]
[Garcia clears his throat]
-Captain. you got a minute?
-Of course.
[splutters] Y'all hear
about that time
that. um. Donaldson pulled over
Billy Martin?
Don't go anywhere.
It's a classic.
-[man 1] Not movin'.
-[man 2] All right. captain.
What's goin' on. Garcia?
[music mutes]
I'm retired. Garcia.
All that shit is
someone else's problem now.
Yeah. Shawn Figueroa was
only talkin' to a few of us
before he died.
There's a rumor out there
that dirty cops put him down.
Whatever you tryin' to say.
don't dance around that shit.
Say it out loud.
I'm not sayin' anything. captain.
I'm asking.
Well. I don't appreciate
what you askin'. detective.
Just because I'm a civilian now
doesn't mean I won't put you
on your ass. Garcia.
[grim music playing]
[inhales sharply] Tanner told me
that your retirement
wasn't voluntary.
That it was forced on you.
I'ma do you a favor
and forget we had
this conversation.
I'ma forget it.
And I'ma go back inside
to my retirement party
and celebrate my thirty five
years of loyal service
to this fuckin' city
and its people.
I'm gon' do that.
You gon' fuck
right the hell off.
♪♪
[music fades]
[Breeze] Just give me a name...
I can have our people
go even up the score.
I'm good. man.
This on me.
Maybe you should lay low
for a minute. though.
[groans]
Crew see you like this...
they might think
they sniffin' weakness.
Might test you.
I wish a nigga would.
You ain't scared of nobody.
Scared of me.
My man.
'Cause we had to burn
your other shit
after the work we put in
at the boxing spot.
It's gon' have niggas
hearin' you comin'
from five blocks away.
My moms tried to break me off
a new ride once.
[dramatic music playing]
Gave that shit back...
'cause ain't nothin' free.
Shit's yours.
I don't need nothin'
back for it.
I keep tellin' you we brothers.
That might not mean
nothin' to you.
That shit mean everything to me.
Shit's dope as hell.
Thanks. man.
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
Ms. Thomas.
Come on in.
[birds chirping]
Since you...
was on the wagon
when you left...
don't feel right to pour out
no liquor.
[laughs softly]
But I brought some
for you anyway.
Do what you want with it.
Don't know what to say
about your nephew.
Can't even wrap
my head around that shit.
Never will.
But I'm all fucked up
out here. Lou-Lou.
[inhales deeply]
Don't even know what I'm doin'.
Never been like this before.
Don't have no feel for the game.
[inhales deeply]
I keep askin' myself
questions...
but I ain't got no answers.
[sighs] I wanna do right by you.
Thing is...
I don't know
what that look like.
But I gotta do somethin'.
[somber music playing]
I gotta feel somethin'.
Fuck.
I miss you. Lou.
[exhales softly]
[inhales deeply. sighs]
[music fades]
Appreciate you seein' me.
I was surprised
to hear from you.
The last time we met.
when Lou was at
the rehabilitation facility.
you seemed skeptical of...
psychiatry. generally. and...
distrustful of me. specifically.
Never said I ain't trust you.
Just wasn't sold on what
you was sayin' about Lou.
Hmm.
And what I said about you
as well.
If memory serves. I made
a remark about your anger
that you didn't appreciate.
You was talkin' about me
when I was payin' you
to talk about my brother.
And who are you paying me to
talk about today. Ms. Thomas?
I was wondering if Lou said
anything about me
you think I should know.
[Dr. Caldwell] I see.
My conversations with
your brother were confidential
at the time that we had them
and they remain so.
even after his passing.
You shared stuff he said before.
I shared what your brother
allowed me to share.
Lou gone.
What harm it gonna do to tell me
some of what he said?
What are you hoping
to hear. Ms. Thomas?
What is it you'd like
Lou to have said about you?
I don't know.
Just tryin' to remember him.
That's all.
It may be that whatever
you're hoping
your brother said about you
is less about what he thought
about you...
but more so what you think
of yourself.
[somber music playing]
You makin' this shit about me
just like you did before.
When you're in this office.
on that couch.
it is about you. Ms. Thomas.
It's always about you.
[music fades]
[engine shuts off]
[Baptiste] Garcia!
You fucked up my party
last night. you motherfucker.
[ominous music playing]
Now I'ma fuck up yours.
I'm just sayin'. shit's ill.
That's all.
[music fades]
Can't get caught slippin'.
[groans]
Fuck y'all doin' here?
Y'all need to be out there
servin' up this work.
[Krank] Niggas shook about
what happened at the crib.
Saw they life flash
in front of 'em and shit.
So you stop workin'?
We ain't been seein' you.
And now it look like that 'cause
you got a little fucked up.
Sometime a nigga
gotta take a minute.
Fuck you just say to me?
I- I-I'm just sayin'.
sometime... you gotta
take a step back
and reassess.
Get your life in order.
Shit's scary out here.
Whoa.
-Damn!
-Oh. fuck!
-Whoa!
-What the hell?!
Man. what the fuck?
[Kanan] Anybody else scared?
[dramatic music playing]
'Cause I can't have
no scared niggas around me.
You scared.
we gon' get you unscared.
You shook.
we gon' get you unshook.
Get the fuck back to work!
-Yeah.
[indistinct chatter]
[Baptiste] You know
how this shit works. Garcia.
You only as good
as your clearance rate.
But shoe leather doesn't always
get the job done.
Sometimes we have to wade
into the very shit
that we tryin' to clean up.
But that shit can stick to you.
Can't always clean it off.
Who were you talkin' to
about Shawn Figueroa?
There's a quid pro quo
to this work.
To get information.
you have to give information.
And that's the choice
you have to make:
"What do I know that feels
safe enough to share?"
And that Figueroa kid felt safe.
He dropped a stick-up kid
the whole neighborhood hated.
It felt like the safest
of the safe shit.
I didn't know...
they were gonna have him killed.
And if they used police...
they weren't from our precinct.
Who made the call?
Oh. some old-time gangsters.
Barely even in the game anymore.
I need a name.
Shoo...
Ishmael and Stephanie Henry.
Snaps and Pop.
[tense. ominous music playing]
[sighs]
Man. you got to believe me.
I had no idea they was gonna
do that kid like that.
And even now. I can't be
so certain that they did.
They just had such a...
hard-on for that Raquel Thomas.
Anything that tracked to her
was something
they wanted to know.
And I knew that
the Figueroa kid was...
friends with Raquel Thomas' son.
So I threw 'em a bone.
[music intensifies]
I had no idea
it would end up how it did.
[inhales sharply]
The feds are all over this.
-They're all over you.
-[Baptiste] I know.
I know.
And it's far bigger
than Figueroa.
It's Howard.
It's Burke. It's the whole...
fuckin' ball of wax.
You're about the only...
clean cop in the 117. Garcia.
Take a fucking bow.
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
[Flossie] They say that.
over time.
losing someone you love
gets easier.
but... that's horseshit.
Time's only made me sadder.
It's made me miss Shira
even more.
So. fuck time
and fuck all the people
that say it gets easier.
You feel better
after you took out the nigga
who killed your daughter?
[sighs]
I didn't.
And I don't regret what I did.
but I don't feel any better.
I don't miss my daughter
any less.
But you got even.
-Even's good.
-Even's gornisht. Marvin.
Even is worse than losing.
It's nothing.
It's nowhere. It's purgatory.
We're not here playing for even.
We're playing to win.
Look. what do I know?
I'm just some Jewish broad
from the Upper East Side.
but if you ask me.
your best and only chance
at winning this thing
is your daughter.
Go all in on her. Marvin.
She's your pocket aces
and your silver bullet.
Bet the fucking house on her.
[solemn music playing]
I get it.
I know you do.
L'chaim. Marvin.
L'chaim.
[music fades]
No one did more
to protect Raq than me.
I mean. fixin' all the shit
she broke.
buildin' back
the bridges she burned.
But you-you-you can't
help someone
that doesn't wanna help
themselves.
And when they're drowning.
like she is.
you gotta get as far away
as you can...
or she'll drag you under
with her.
[sighs]
[gentle traditional music
playing in shop]
She has not been
a reliable partner.
She guaranteed me
a specific volume of demand
that she has not met.
Well. my young friend here.
he can meet and surpass
those demands. Hafiz.
And you won't get
all the bullshit
that comes along with Raq.
We movin' so much work right now
we can't keep up.
What about
your current supplier?
Well...
We got enough room
for everybody.
And we gon' give you
a five percent bump
on what Raq has been payin'.
Your friends in Manhattan
won't like that we're abandoning
them and their business.
I'll handle Pino.
You don't need to worry
about that.
[Hafiz] Why are you extending
this offer to us?
Surely you have relationships
with other importers.
Unless you are doing this
simply to undermine
Raquel Thomas.
You ever hear the expression.
"Don't look a gift horse
in the mouth"?
'Cause from where I'm standin'.
you look like you got
a lot of horse
and we're offering you
a hell of a gift.
You should take it.
[dramatic music playing]
-We accept.
-Ah!
A wise decision.
-Ah-ah.
-Mm-hmm.
There you go. huh?
[muttering]
[music transitions
into somber music]
[music intensifies]
[music turns ominous]
[music further intensifies]
[gun cocks]
[gunshot]
[dark. dramatic music playing]
[ominous tolling of bell
in music]
[music fades]
[Marvin] I wanted you two
to meet
because if anything
were to happen to me...
What's gonna happen to you?
I'm just saying.
If anything happens.
I want you to know each other.
I'm not plannin'
on goin' nowhere no time soon.
but...
nobody ever is.
You step off that curb...
[sighs]
Those buses move real fast.
I don't want you to go anywhere.
Uncle Marvin.
Don't worry.
He got me.
and I'll always be holdin'
his old-ass hand
when he cross the street.
[Marvin laughs] My girls.
All worried about me.
Those police
still tryin' to scare you?
They came by again.
They said another neighbor
saw a Black guy
coming out of the house
when that happened.
[Marvin] They just lyin'. though.
You didn't fall for that.
I told them I wasn't sure.
I was so scared. I couldn't
really remember for sure.
Uh...
Ah...
Go play on them swings.
Be over in a minute.
[solemn music playing]
What'd you do?
Can't really get into it
right now.
But it's on some "no good deed"
"goes unpunished" type shit.
Guess I'ma need you
to get that cop to look into it.
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
We gotta hit the fuck back. man.
That's my mom's shit
at my old spot:
my uncle runnin' up like he did.
We need to run up on that club.
start blastin'.
You wanna hit them
like you hit Krank.
[Kanan] I made an example
out of Krank.
I'ma make a meal out my mom.
You gon' put down Raq?
This ain't about
puttin' her down.
It's about showin' her
who the fuck we are.
And what the fuck that gon' do
for us and this work?
She came at us.
We goin' back at her.
She came at you. nigga.
Not us.
This between y'all.
The rest of us
just collateral damage
in y'all bullshit.
Look. there's a time and place
for everything.
But we gotta be strategic.
Can't just buck off.
You gotta measure and mark
a motherfucker
before you make your move.
[sinister music playing]
You heard?
[music intensifies]
[music fades]
My decision is final.
Well what happened to all of
that. "In my country".
"it's better to be dead
than break a promise" bullshit?
'Cause you made a whole lot
of fuckin' noise
about all that. Hafiz.
We have found another partner
who offers
increased demand
and a better price.
So you fuckin'
with somebody else.
Okay.
But why that mean
you gotta dead our shit?
I would never get in the way
of you gettin' paid.
You can work
with the both of us.
We cannot.
[grim music playing]
You fuckin' wit' Stefano
and all of them.
He makin' you kick me
to the curb.
You must leave now.
[Ishaq] Let's go.
[music intensifies]
You talk about how hard
motherfuckers are
where you from. Hafiz?
You don't know shit
about where I'm from.
You about to find out.
[Garcia] Snaps and Pop.
[music fades]
They killed Fame?
With some help from the police.
Don't know which cops exactly.
It wasn't Buckley and Roland.
But it was NYPD.
Just like I told you.
Look. Uh...
I don't know what made me think
I could do this with you.
I can't.
Here's the money you gave me.
Every dollar.
I'm done.
Hearin' how all these other guys
are on the take.
it makes me realize
that I'm not them.
Assumin' you keep
your nose clean.
I'll leave you alone.
I won't bother you anymore.
I don't want anything to do
with you or this.
[laughs softly]
Barely knew what the fuck
I was doing
with all this shit anyway.
[laughs]
[inhales sharply]
Yeah. that makes two of us.
[inhales deeply]
I do need one more favor
from you. Garcia.
One last thing
for you to look into.
[dramatic music playing]
[inhales deeply. sighs]
It's not like I was planning
on doing this work
for the rest of my life.
This was always gonna be
a short stop for me.
I don't know that you were
really ever cut out for it.
And a big part of this job
is showing up.
and that's clearly
not your strong suit.
I appreciate the opportunity.
Best of luck. Jarita.
You too.
[tense music playing]
[music intensifies]
[music builds]
[gun cocks]
You're lucky this rug is new.
[music fades]
[engine rumbling]
[engine shuts off]
[Marvin] This don't feel right.
How many more wars you tryin'
to have at the same time?
As many as it take to win.
[dramatic music playing]
[door opens]
[gun cocks]
What is this. you and Jarita
thought you could rob me
or something idiotic like that?
That's not what this about.
Then what?
You workin' with Raq.
I got beef wit' her.
And who the fuck are you
exactly?
[music intensifies]
Her son.
Oh. you gotta be
fucking kidding me.
[scoffs]
♪♪
Don't have time for this.
Ain't gonna take long.
[older Kanan] When shit go bad.
it takes on a life of its own.
Gets its own strength.
-[silenced gunshot]
-[groans]
[older Kanan] Its own momentum.
And once that happens.
you gon' run outta options
real fast. nigga.
You gon' make hard decisions
that's gonna hurt you
and everybody around you.
And once all that bad shit
start happenin'.
you gon' think you can stop it
by doin' your own ill shit.
But all that's gonna do
is give it more energy.
[grunting]
-[silenced gunshots]
-[groans]
[older Kanan] More power.
[squelching]
[music intensifies]
[older Kanan]
And before you know it...
your shit goin' from bad...
to worse.
♪ Now the funeral is over ♪
♪ And all the tears
Are dried up ♪
♪ Niggas hangin' deep
On the cut. gettin' fired up ♪
♪ Lookin' for the nigga who
Pulled his pistol on my homie ♪
♪ An eye for an eye. so now
Your life is what you owe me ♪
♪ Look deep into the eyes
Of your motherfuckin' killer ♪
♪ I want you to witness your
Motherfuckin' murder. nigga ♪
♪ And since you wants to kill
Then your ass has gots to fry ♪
♪ But ain't no police ♪
♪ Therefore your ass
Has gots to die ♪
♪ We play the game for keeps ♪
♪ And if you slipped
I guess you sleep ♪
♪ You sho' nuff fucked and now
Your ass is six feet deep ♪
♪ 'Cause where I come from
Yo. everybody's got a gat ♪
♪ And niggas try your ass ♪
♪ Just to see
Where you got your heart at ♪
♪ And if your shit is flimsy
Then your ass is gonna bend ♪
♪ And like I said before ♪
♪ There'll be no tears
In the end ♪
♪ I'm rollin' through
Your hood ♪
♪ And now my heart
Is filled with anger ♪
♪ You at your sister's house ♪
♪ And now your sister's life's
In danger ♪
♪ By a total stranger ♪
♪ With a gang of niggas
Wantin' to bang you ♪
♪ And hang you. stain you ♪
♪ With one up in the chamber ♪
♪ Let's take a trip
Up Holloway ♪
♪ So you can see
How many niggas in my hood ♪
♪ Is down to die today ♪
♪ We standin' up
For our own shit ♪
♪ And if you outside the clique
Then you die. bitch ♪
♪ Quick ♪
♪ It ain't no love
In this motherfucker ♪
♪ It ain't no love for yourself
Or your other brother ♪
♪ Uh. because we real
With this shit ♪
♪ So we stay true ♪
♪ And since we bang
Then we do what OG... ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-